- Sometimes, making a big decision at work
-有時，在工作中做出重大決定
can feel like you're answering the final question
可能會感覺像您正在回答比賽節目中
on a game show, everyone's watching and time is running out.
的最後一個問題，每個人都在觀看，而且時間不足。
Are you gonna win the big prize,
你會贏得大獎
or are you gonna go home empty-handed?
還是空手回家？
It's easy to start doubting yourself.
開始懷疑自己很容易。
Now, you'd probably feel more confident making a decision
現在，如果您只有更多信息，您可
if you just had more information.
能會更加自信做決定。
Usually that means doing in-depth research
通常這意味著進行深入的研究
and pulling together things like competitor profiles
，並將競爭對手資料和消費者趨勢
and consumer trends and industry insights.
和行業見解等內容整合在一起。
But creating just one of those reports could take days
但是只建立其中一份報告可能需要數天
or weeks, or even months.
或數週，甚至數月。
Now, this is where AI can be an incredibly
現在，這就是 AI 可以成為非常有價值的研究合
valuable research partner.
作夥伴的地方。
It does way more than just produce a report faster.
它不僅僅僅是更快地生成報告。
It can scour a range of sources, get to the key takeaways,
它可以搜索各種來源，了解主要的結果，並幫助
and help you deliver a stronger report.
您提供更強大的報告。
It's a whole new way of conducting research
這是對某個主
and building understanding on a topic.
題進行研究和建立了理解的全新方式。
Now, let's be clear, this doesn't mean that the fundamentals
現在，讓我們清楚說明，這並不意味著良好研
of good research are going away.
究的基礎知識將消失。
You still need to verify all of your information,
您仍然需要驗證所有信息，並
and you still need to build your own arguments.
且仍然需要構建自己的參數。
And when you're faced with really difficult
當您面臨非常困難
or ambiguous challenges, the ones where there's
或模糊的挑戰時，這些挑戰真的沒有
really no simple solution, you still need to consider
簡單的解決方案，您仍然需要考慮
all the angles and make the final decision.
所有角度並做出最終決定。
In this course, you'll learn how you can use AI
在本課程中，您將學習如何使用 AI 在幾乎任
to build deeper understanding in almost any area,
何領域建立更深入的理解，並
and you'll discover how to transform uncertainty
發現如何將不確定性轉化
into solid, confident recommendations.
為堅實、自信的建議。
First, we'll show you how to research a complex topic
首先，我們將向您展示如何使用
with Gemini Deep Research.
Gemini 深度研究一個複雜的主題。
It can find and analyze multiple sources on your behalf,
它可以代表您找到和分析多個來源，
synthesize that information,
合成該信息
and reason through its findings.
並通過其發現理論。
Then you'll gain the ability to cut directly
然後，即使最重要的碎片分散
to key takeaways from any materials that come your way,
在多個文件中，您也可以從任何出現的材料中直接切
even if the most important nuggets
出來的重要摘要的
are scattered across multiple documents.
能力。
You'll learn how to manage that information,
您將學習如何管理這些信息，
reports, articles, websites, business documents,
報告，文章，網站，業務文檔，
meeting notes, almost anything,
會議筆記，幾乎所有內容，
and generate useful summaries in text, audio,
並
and video formats using NotebookLM.
使用 NotebookLM 生成文本，音頻和視頻格式的有用摘要。
Finally, you'll create a Gem, which is a custom AI expert
最後，您將創建一個 Gem，這是一個自定義的 AI 專家，可以在
for help on any topic to get your questions answered,
任何主題上提供幫助，以獲得答案的問題，
or just a place to bounce around ideas.
或者只是一個可以反映想法的地方。
After completing this course, you'll be able to consistently
完成此課程後，您將能夠一致地將複
turn complexity into clarity.
雜性轉化為清晰度。
You'll be well on your way to being the person
您將很好地成為同事所依賴的人
that colleagues rely on to tackle tough, ambiguous problems.
來解決艱難而不明確的問題。
And with the feedback from Gemini,
借助雙子座的反饋，
you'll always feel like you have support
您將始終感到自己在做出重大決
in making huge decisions.
策方面獲得支持。
It's a shift that gives you the power
這是一個轉變，讓您能
to enhance your understanding on almost any topic.
夠增強對幾乎任何主題的理解。
So, if getting a new way to learn quickly
因此，如果找到一種快速學習的新方法
sounds good to you, then let's get started.
對您來說聽起來很好，那麼讓我們開始。